Finding Aid for the Michael A. Kaschak Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Michael A. Kaschak Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0558
.42 linear_feet
Biography/History
Michael A. Kaschak attended Vanderbilt University, graduating in 1933 with a Bachelor of Arts Degree.
Scope and Contents
This .21 linear foot collection contains 49 photographs, in 31 folders, of sites around Tennessee; buildings in Nashville, Tennessee; and, buildings on the campuses of George Peabody College and Vanderbilt University.
- Tennessee – Outside Nashville
  - Lookout Mountain, June 9, 1932 – (1) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Moccasin Bend and Lookout Battlefield, 1932 – (1) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mountain Home – (1) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Narrows – waterfall – (1) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    [dug by slaves during the Civil War]
- Tennessee - Nashville
  - Fisk University Library, 1932 – (1) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fort Nashborough, November 15, 1931 – (2) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hermitage, March 25, 1928 – (3) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    [Andrew Jackson Home]
  - Jackson Square – (1) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Square – (1) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Parthenon, 1932 – (6) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Percy Warner Park – (3) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Scarritt Center Tower – (3) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Show-boat on Cumberland River, November 15, 1931 – (1) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee State Capitol – (2) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Union Station – (1) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- George Peabody College
  - Administration Building – (1) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Entrance – Side – (1) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics Building – (1) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Arts Building (aka Mayborn Building) – (1) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Library – (1) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Psychology Building (aka Jessup) – (1) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Social Religious Building – (1) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Vanderbilt University
  - Buttrick Hall, 1930 – (1) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Calhoun Hall, 1930 – (2) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - College Hall (aka Kirkland Hall) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Furman Hall, 1930 – (2) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Graduate School (aka YMCA Building) – (3) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Medical School Building – (1) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Neely Chapel – (1) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Science Hall – (1) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Wesley Hall, November, 1931 – (2) (Box 1, Folder 31)